trucksuvidha.com 2017-12-18

# PrivacyPolicy, Load/Cargo/Freight, Truck/Lorry, TruckSuvidha

We value the trust you place on us. That's why we insist upon the highest standards for secure transactions and customer information privacy. Please read the following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

**Note:** Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically. By visiting this Website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our Website. By mere use of the Website, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Use. 

  * ## Information Collection:-

    * When you use our website, we collect and store your personal information which is provided by you from time to time. Our primary goal in doing so is to provide you a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our Website to make your experience safer and easier. More importantly, while doing so we collect personal information from you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose.
    * In general, you can browse the website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature on the Website. We may automatically track certain information about you based upon your behavior on our Website. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve our users.
  * ### Use of Demographic / Profile Data / Your Information

    * We use personal information to provide the services you request. To the extent we use your personal information to market to you, we will provide you the ability to opt-out such uses. We use your personal information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, help promote a safe service, collect money, measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates, customize your experience, detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity, enforce our terms and conditions, and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.
    * In our efforts to continually improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our users' activity on our Website.
    * We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.
    * We will occasionally ask you to complete optional online surveys. These surveys may ask you for contact information and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). We use this data to tailor your experience at our Website, providing you with content that we think you might be interested in and to display content according to your preferences.
  * ### Cookies

    * Cookies are pieces of information that are automatically stored in a person’s hard drive upon his use of the website. TruckSuvidha uses cookies to enable the browser to track the information provided to us by a user. The cookies do not contain any sort of viruses and are used for security and customization purposes. If a user rejects cookies, he may not be able to have access to some of the features or the services offered by the website.
  * ### Sharing of Personal Information

    * We may share personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates to help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts, correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services, and to facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity. Those entities and affiliates may not market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-in. 
    * We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court
    * Orders or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy, respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party, or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public.
    * We and our affiliates will share / sell some or all of your personal information with another business entity we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity, or re-organization, amalgamation, restructuring of business. Such a transaction occurs that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information.
  * ### Security

    * Our Website has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.
  * ### Links to other websites

    * Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
  * ### Posting Your Information to Public Areas of [trucksuvidha.com](http://trucksuvidha.com/ "India's freight and truck matching portal. Book truck load online.")

    * Please remember that if you post any of your personal information in public areas of [trucksuvidha.com](http://trucksuvidha.com/ "India's freight and truck matching portal. Book truck load online."),, such as in online forums or chat rooms, or in the searchable database, such information may be collected and used by others over whom Sarvodaya Infotech Pvt. Ltd. has no control. We cannot control the use made by third parties of information you post or otherwise make available in public areas of Sarvodaya Infotech Pvt. Ltd..
  * ### Controlling and Managing your personal information

    * We retain all the information we gather about you in an effort to make your repeat use with us more efficient, practical and relevant until you change or remove your personal data as described below. You may have access to review, correct, update, or delete your account profile information at any time. Simply log into your account, go to your profile, and make the necessary changes. Before providing you with a copy of your personal information or correcting, updating or deleting such information, we reserve the right to verify and authenticate your identity and the personal information to which you have requested access. Access to or correction, updating or deletion of your personal information may be denied or limited by Sarvodaya Infotech Pvt. Ltd. if it would violate another person(s) rights and/or as otherwise permitted by applicable law.
    * If you wish to delete or close your account or account profile information altogether, please contact us at customercare@trucksuvidha.com. An email will be sent to you to confirm that your personal information has been deleted (save for an archival copy which is not accessible by you or third parties on the Internet). The archival copy is retained as long as Sarvodaya Infotech Pvt. Ltd. reasonably considers necessary for audit and record purposes. We will also retain logs, demographic, indirect, and statistical information that may relate to you but do not identify you personally. If your personal information was previously accessed by others using our Sites, we are not able to delete the information or copies thereof from their systems.
  * ### Your Consent

    * By using the Website and/ or by providing your information, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the Website in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to your consent for sharing your information as per this privacy policy.
    * If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

### Grievance Officer 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below or drop us a mail with subject line-PRIVACY POLICY:

**Sarvodaya Infotech Pvt. Ltd.**  
**Address:** 2nd Floor, Kamla Nagar, Jagadhri Road, Near Telephone Exchange, Yamunanagar, Haryana, India,135001   
**Contact No:** +91 8882-08-08-08, +91 9996-40-17-32   
**E-mail:**[info@trucksuvidha.com](mailto:info@trucksuvidha.com "TruckSuvidha Email-id")
